Register of the Argentina. Consulado General (Berlin) Records, 1929-1944
Hoover Institution Archives
Argentina. Consulado General (Berlin) Records,
1929-1944
66011
Argentina. Consulado General (Berlin)
1 manuscript box (0.4 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, reports, and clippings, relating to Argentine-German relations, especially trade relations.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Access Points
Argentina; Argentina--Foreign relations--Germany; Germany; Germany--Foreign relations--Argentina
Container List
- Banco Aleman Transatlantico (Deutsche Uberseeische Bank, Berlin), 1929-1942. Set of instructions to transfer money from the account of the Argentine Consulate in Berlin to a special account at the Deutsche Bank in Hamburg for "Argentinisches Generalkonsulat, Ministero de Hazienda de la Nacion Argentina" (Box 1.)
- Miscellaneous materials
  - Argentina. Consulado (Berlin), 1941-1943
  - Argentine trade, 1939
  - Deutsche Bank, 1941-1943
  - Deutsch-Spanische Gesellschaft, 1941-1944
- Fiebrig, Professor Dr. Clippings on Argentine industry and correspondence, 1936
- List of addresses and names, covering mostly Argentina
- List of Argentine citizens living in the jurisdiction of the Argentine consulate in Leipzig
- Faupel. Correspondence, 1938-1940. Includes material of the Ibero-Amerikanisches Institut